约翰 知道基督吗...
Hey,John,you know actually about Jesus,
替我向他问好吧
say hi to him for me,will you?
是他
It's him.
-你看到他了吗  -谁
-Did you see him?  -Who?
观刑室的那家伙
The guy in the viewing room.
-没有  -是爸爸
-No.  -It was Dad.
你的女孩呢
Where's your girl?
她大约一小时后回到我的住所
She'll be at my place in about an hour.
很快 主动权就掌握在我们手里了
Pretty soon,we're gonna call in our favor.
好好享用吧
Have at it.
老大
Boss!
上头给你一个小时见儿子
The Department of Corrections is allowing you a one-hour visit with your son.
我去安排这次行程 但我不想出现任何问题
I'll make the travel arrangements,but I don't want any problems.
我以前有一只丹麦种大狗 又大又忠诚
You know,I used to have a Great Dane,big and loyal.
12岁的时候得了癌症 我们不得不让她安息
But when she was 12,she got cancer,so we had to put her down.
你可能会认为这是件很难下手的事情 但...
And you'd think it would be this big,dramatic event,but...
其实过程非常的平静
it was very peaceful.
一分钟前她还在呼吸 之后就停止了
One minute she was breathing,the next she wasn't.
没事吧 需要我拨911急救电话吗
Everything okay? Need me to call 911?
不 不 不用了
No,no,I got it.
引擎冒烟很厉害 看起来随时会爆炸
That engine's smoking pretty bad,looks like it could go up any second.
-我觉得不会  -你这么认为?
-We'll be okay,actually.  -You think?
-是  -如果你这么说的话 那好吧
-Yeah.  -All right,if you say so.
没事 我想没什么事
Fine.I think it's going to be fine.
苏克雷·费尔南多禁闭期满释放
Fernando Sucre released from Ad Seg.
堂哥
Cuz!
你出来了
You're out.
见到你真好
It's good to see you,buddy.
你们以后再叙旧吧
You all can sign each other's yearbooks later.
进度怎么样了
Where are we at?
地图搞定了
The map is complete.
我拿到了我要的部分
I got what I needed.
-那么一切准备就绪  -差不多了
-Then we're ready.  -Almost.
我现在知道应该如何走精神病区下面的管道了
I know which pipes we need to take to go beneath Psych Ward now.
就是说通向医务室的路线是没问题了
Which means our way to the Infirmary is clear.
走这条新路线
With our new route,
我们要到达这幢大楼的最远一端
we're gonna come up on the far end of that building.
就是说我们得穿过30英尺长的走廊才能到达医生办公室
Which means we gotta walk down 30 feet of hallway to get to the doctor's office...
也就是我们的出口
our exit point.
整个计划还缺一个环节
Which means there's only one piece left to this whole thing.
进那扇门的钥匙
The key to that room.
不是太难
No sweat.
我们要做的只是造成另一起"意外"的碰撞和上次一样
That's all we gotta do is run a bump and grab on a CO like we did last time,
拿到钥匙 复制一把
grab the keys,make a copy.
没那么简单
It's not that easy.
只有医疗队才有那钥匙
Only the medical staff have those keys.
那你有什么招数么 美人儿
How're you fixing on getting it then pretty?
小心行事
Carefully.
这次不要再出意外了 好吗
No more surprises this time,right?
好
Right.
老天啊...
Jesus
我的老天
Mary,and Joseph.
-好啊 约翰  -迈克尔
-Hello,John.  -Michael.
你好吗
How are you?
能活着已经是福气了 感谢上帝
Any day above ground is a blessing.Thanks be to God.
介意一起坐吗 请
Do you mind? Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
谣言挺多
Lot of rumors going around.
是啊
Yeah.
很高兴你回来了
I'm glad you're back.
很惊讶你居然还在这儿
I'm surprised you're still here.
我还以为你已经走了
I thought you'd be gone by now.
中间出了些错
Well,we had a few setbacks.
还计划着那事吗
Still planning on it?
这取决于...
That depends...
你是否还想跟我们一块儿走
How does the idea of escaping sit with the new you?
那个曾经被关押的罪人他已经死了
Oh,the old sinner who was confined to these walls he's dead.
新的灵魂理应得到自由
The new soul deserves to be free.
以前的罪人会给我们准备一架飞机
Well,the old sinner was gonna have a jet ready for us.
新的灵魂还能否办到
Is the new soul gonna be able to pull that off?
诺亚拥有一只方舟 难道我没有
Noah had his Ark,didn't I?
让我们祈祷吧
Let's pray.
我要一把刀子 急需
I'm gonna need a blade.Pronto.
-肇事逃跑  -是的 长官
-Hit and run?  -Yes,sir.
-布伦斯跑了  -是的
-And Burrows is gone?  -That's right.
-警卫呢  -两个死了 一个危在旦夕
-The officers?  -Two are dead,one is in critical.
你知道被媒体知道这件事后 他们会怎么说吗
Do you realize what the media's gonna say when they get ahold of this?
我们会把他抓回来 长官
We'll get him back,sir.
这行干了40年 到头来确给他们留下这么个印象
40 years in corrections,and this is how they're gonna remember me.
这是在凯恩郡 巴雷德警长是我的一个好朋友
This is Kane County.Sheriff Ballard's a good friend of mine.
他还没跟任何人说过
He hasn't said a word to anyone yet.
给我们4到5个小时 我们会把他抓回来的
Yeah,well...Give us four,five hours,we'll find him.
如果我现在不向纠正部门报告 那么...
If I don't report this to the D.O.C.Right now...
他们没必要知道
They don't have to know.
你总是按章程办事 头儿
You've always been a by-the-book guy,boss,
但这次 那些章程会炒了我们鱿鱼
but this time,the book's gonna get us all fired.
找到他
Find him.
这些是魁恩手机的所有电话纪录 打进的 打出的
The records of every phone call made to and from every contact in Quinn's cell phone.
这就好比是大海 我们去哪里捞针呢
Well,we have our haystack. Any idea what the needle might look like?
这里有几千个电话
There must be thousands of calls here.
问题是打给谁的 打到哪里的
But to who? To where?
知道吗 我们一辈子都查不完这些电话纪录
You know,it's gonna take us forever to go through all of these.
万一这些和林肯还有斯蒂德曼的事毫无关系怎么办
And what if these have nothing to do with Lincoln and Steadman,huh?
万一这纯粹是在浪费时间呢
What if we're just burning time?
要改判死刑 我们总是差那么一步
We're just that much closer to the execution.
你这是怎么了 尼克 我的意思是好像你想放弃了
What's going on with you,Nick? I mean,it's almost like you want to quit.
我不想放弃
I don't want to quit.
那就开始干活吧
Then let's get to it.
唐克雷蒂医生马上就到
Dr.Tancredi will be right in.
-早上好   -早上好
-Morning.  -Morning.
你感觉...感觉怎么样
How're you feeling today?
-好多了   -不错
-Better.  -Good.
我们在塞奇桥的117号公路上
We got checkpoints up at 171 by Lemont,
以及在通往罗密欧的河道边都设了关卡
at Sage Bridge and at the river going towards Romeoville.
那边的目击者说
According to our witness over there
嫌疑人驾驶的是一辆06年产的野马牌轿车 黑色或许是深蓝色
this new perp was driving an '06 Mustang,black,dark blue,maybe.
这件事隐瞒不了多久的 布拉德
We're not gonna be able to sit on this thing very long,Brad.
这是为了我 内特 我需要你这么做
This is me,Nate.I need this.
好吧
All right.
你回狐狸河吧 我会和你保持联系
You go back to Fox River.I'll be in constant contact.
你介意我...
You mind if I...
没事吧 先生
How're you doing,Mr...
-我是罗伊·霍金斯  -你好
-Roy Hawkings.  -Hi.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我不得不先走了
I'd like to get going if I could.
我在奥罗拉还有个会议快迟到了
I'm late for a meeting in Aurora.
-你从哪来的   -芝加哥
-Where you coming from?  -Chicago.
往这边走去奥罗拉是在绕远路啊
Kind of an indirect route to get to Aurora.
我对这儿不熟
I'm not from around here.
如果发现任何线索
If any of you get so much as a whiff of anything,
马上通知我
I want to know about it immediately.
也通知我 伙计
Makes two of us,pal.
你想要什么 迈克尔
What do you want from me,Michael?
莎拉...
Sara...
我要你为我做件事
I need you to do something for me.
什么
What?
等着我
Wait for me.
我不会一辈子这个样子的
It won't always be like this.
在这房间 这个地方
In this room,in this place.
不到那个时候 我们不能这么做
Until then,I can't.
不能这么做
We can't.
该死的
Damn it.
我不能这么做
I can't.
我得走了
And I gotta go.
-老婆 你来了  -艾弗卡托
-Hey,squirt. -Avocado.
我得说多少次
How many times I gotta say it?
你要叫得正式一点
You address me formal like.
-博斯·约翰逊先生   -这样好多了
-Mr.Balls Johnson  -That's better.
我想你和我可以解决点事儿
I think maybe you and I can work something out.
是吗
Really?
是的 听着 我外面有个朋友
Check it,I got this homie on the outside
他可以每个月给你户头上存100块
and he can put a hundie into your commissary account each month.
感谢你想得这么周到
It was nice of you to think of me like that,
但你只有一样我要的
but you only got one thing I need.
我要你帮我办点事儿 再来一次撞击偷窃
I need you to get something for me.Do your bump and swipe thing.
-像上次偷表那样   -对
-Like I did with the watch?  -Exactly.
上次给了我很多好处啊
Yeah,that did me a lot of good.
警卫发现了 他们把我和艾弗卡托关一个房间
Guards found out and they stuck me into a cell with Avocado.
所以如果你想要我偷东西 你也得为我做点事儿
So if you want something glommed,you need to do something for me.
帮我杀了那家伙
Kill that son of a bitch.
这不是我所能办到的
That's not something I can do.
操他妈的霍纳斯·瓦格纳
Screw Honus Wagner.
那是什么
What was that?
我邻居的小孩儿
This kid in my neighborhood,
他老爸专收集棒球卡...
his dad had a baseball card collection.
所以我想...偷那些卡片
So I figured,you know,I'd swipe it.
然后卖掉 去派对玩儿
I could get some party cash,you know?
里面有一张卡片
And there was one card in there.
是一张1910年的"霍纳斯·瓦格纳"棒球卡
A 1910 Honus Wagner.
对我来说没什么用 我喜欢的是篮球
Doesn't mean nothing to me,you know.Hoops is my sport.
这张卡片 价值30万美金
This card,it was worth $300,000.
所以他们把我定为特大盗窃罪
So they slapped me with grand larceny.
所以我才会来这儿的
That's why I'm here.
所以我才会被判刑5年 最后搞得跟个臭娘们一样
That's why I'm sitting on a nickel getting turned out like a little bitch.
一张棒球卡
A baseball card.
爸爸
Dad?
你在这做什么
What are you doing here?
我接到他们让你见你儿子最后一面的通知
As soon as I heard they granted you a visit with your son,
我就知道他们要对你动手了
I knew they'd make a move on you.
我是问你在这儿做什么
I mean what are you doing here?
距离这20英里外有辆车
I've got a car about 20 miles from here.
我们去那边换车 然后
We'll switch out.After that,
我会确保没人能找到你
gonna make sure you disappear.
之后一切就是我和他们之间的事了 你可以走吗
Then this business will just be between me and them.Can you move?
你在说什么 他们在追捕我 不是你
What are you talking about? They're after me,not you.
相信我 事情没你想得这么简单
It's not as simple as that,trust me.
我曾经为他们效力
I worked for them.
你曾为他们效力? 你是个酒鬼  一个...
You worked for them?You're an alcoholic...
你记得是这样吗 还是谁跟你这么说的
Is that what you remember or is that what you were told?
你为什么要离开
Why'd you leave?
我在一家跨国集团工作 我们把它称之为"公司"
I took a position with a group of multinationals we call The Company.
他们决定了国家的每一次行动
They call every shot this country takes,
通过法律 委派法官 决定是否进行战争等
what laws to pass,what judges to appoint,what wars to fight.
关键是 如果谁想像我一样晋升职位
Thing is,if you wanted to rise in the ranks like I did,
他们必须承诺放弃以前的一切
you had to commit to leaving everything you know behind.
只有那样 你才有机会接触真正的信息
Because then you start to get access to the real information.
而那些信息有些人甚至会不择手段去得到...
Information people would do a lot of things to get their hands on,
比如牺牲你的家庭
like harm your family.
你要我相信你
You expect me to believe that?
你为什么不联系我们
Why didn't you reach out to us?
你为什么不打电话给我们
Why didn't you call us?
我每天都在忏悔 但我别无选择
I regretted it every day,but I didn't have a choice.
林肯 我离开公司的那天
Lincoln,the day I left The Company,
我带走了所有的信息
I took all that information with me.
所以他们才对你动手
That's why they're doing this to you.
所有的一切 都是为了阻止我
All of it,to stop me.
你得相信我
You have to trust me.
那你就得告诉我发生了什么事
Then you'll have to tell me what's going on.
-我不能那么做   -那我也帮不了你
-I can't do that.  -Then I can't help.
听着 我已经按你说的做了
Look,I did what you ask.
绿卡换信用卡 这是说好了的
Green card for credit card,that was the deal.
那我们再做一次交易
Then,we'll make a new deal.
迈克尔 如果被谁发现的话...
Michael,if somebody find out...
相信我 我比你的麻烦更大
Believe me,I'll be in more trouble than you will.
我知道 所以我才不能帮你
I know,and this is why I won't help you.
听着 尼卡 我向你保证
Look,Nika,I promise you...
我不知道发生了什么事
Look,I don't know what's going on.
我不知道你怎么会去监狱的
I don't know why you're in there,
那些把我带到这儿来的人教我一件事
but if there's one thing those guys that brought me here taught me,
如果你斗争 如果你反抗
is that if you fight,if you struggle,
你只会把事搞得更糟 不要反抗了 迈克尔
you only make things worse.Stop fighting,Michael.
再考虑一下 行吗
Just think about it,okay?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这里又有 这个406号码 每张单子上都有
There it is again,the 406 number.It's on every listing.
4-0-6
406.
有超过两百个商用电话 外加一百个家用电话
Yeah,there's over 200 businesses,another 100 residences
分布在17个国家
in 171 different countries.
他们都拨打这个电话
And they're all calling the same number.
-4-0-6  -蒙大拿
-406.  -Montana.
能查到号码前缀吗
Can you check the prefixes?
这不合逻辑
This doesn't make sense.
全世界的人都在打电话
All these people from all over the world
给这个不知道在哪儿 只有42个人的地方
are calling this place in the middle of nowhere with a population of 42.
布莱克福特 蒙大拿
Blackfoot,Montana.
我还以为你会明白 特伦斯
I thought you understood,Terrence.
如果你想和我谈话 我们在家 面对面谈
If you wanna talk,we set up a meeting,at home,in person.
我看了最近的报导 你的人气有所下降
I saw the latest tracking.Your polls are headed south.
也许布伦斯的案子终于吸引了一些议员们的注意力
Maybe the Burrows thing is finally starting to gain some traction with the swings.
-真是打击  -再见 特伦斯
-It could hurt.  -Goodbye,Terrence.
-你说过一切都快结束了  -是的
-You said it was almost over.  -It is.
我们是在说林肯·布伦斯... 还是你的竞选
Are we talking about Lincoln Burrows ...or your candidacy?
你现在还活着的唯一理由
The only reason that you are still alive
是因为我不让他们杀你
is because I won't let them kill you.
是 这我相当清楚
Yeah.I'm pretty clear on that.
但我不太想得通的是...
But the thing I can't quite figure is,
随着这件事搞得越来越黑...
with the crap storm this thing's become,
他们怎么还没杀了你
why they haven't killed you?
想好怎么去搞医务室钥匙了吗
Figure out how you're gonna get the key to the Infirmary yet?
还没有
Not quite.
你想对她下手还是怎么
You working a game on her,or what?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想了很多
I've had time to think.
没想你要杀了我
Not that you tried to kill me,
而是想上帝如何救了我
but about how Jesus saved me.
我不是来这里报复的
I didn't come here,Theodore,to inflict any more pain.
握住我的手 让我们尽弃前嫌吧
Take my hand so we can put this behind us. Please.
把你的另一只手伸出来
Show me the palm of your other hand.
别再侮辱我 在你干了那事以后
Don't insult me. After all that you've done,
我只要求你 别再侮辱我
the least I ask is that you don't insult me.
温暖的手不是比冰冷的刀片感觉更好么
Does not a warm hand feel better than a cold shank?
你说得很好 约翰 是啊
You got a point there,John. Yeah.
休战吧
Truce?
行 休战
You got it. Truce.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
都已经过去两个半小时了那警长还什么消息都没有
It's been two and a half hours and you're telling me that sheriff has got nothing?
我是来告诉你道路已经全部被封锁了
I'm telling you the roads are blocked off.
那野马车一定是在方圆10英里内的某个地方
That Mustang's got to be somewhere within those 10 square miles.
好吧 听着 再给你两个小时的时间找他
All right,listen,you got two hours to find him.
过后 我不得不向媒体宣布
After that,I have got to talk to the press.
现在有个死刑犯正逃之夭夭
Hey,but there's an escaped killer outside our walls
有些东西比你的职业更重要
and there are some things that are more important than career.
现在给我去找到他
Now you find him!
-长官  -我没时间
-Hey,Captain.  -I don't have time.
他说他想和你谈谈
He says he really needs to talk.
你有什么还是问我要什么
You have something for me or do you need something?
因为如果是后者的话 你纯粹是在浪费时间
'Cause if it's the latter,you just wasted my time.
我现在的狱友 艾弗卡托...
That cellie you stuck me with,Avocado...
你有什么东西还是你需要什么东西
Do you have something or do you need something?
我最后再问一次
Last time I'm gonna ask.
我求你不要再把我和他关一起
I'm asking you to just,please,get me out of that cell.
头儿 求你了 头儿
Boss,please.Boss!
走吧
Let's go.
你要学会放松 就不会太痛了
You need to start relaxing.It'll hurt a lot less.
可以去你的床上做吗
Can we go on your bunk?
当然可以了
Sure,squirt.
让我把这弄得更舒服一点
Let me make it a wee bit more comfortable.
既然说好了的话
Now we're talking.
你是监狱的那个医生
Are you the doctor from the prison?
是 我能帮你...
Yeah.Can,I...
你认识一个叫迈克尔·斯科菲尔德的囚犯吗
Do you know a prisoner named Michael Scofield?
我认识
I do.
-你是他老婆 对吗  -我得和你谈谈
-You're his wife,right?  -I need to talk to you.
我想迈克尔给自己惹大麻烦了
I think Michael has got himself in some trouble.
我想他正计划做些危险的事情
And I think he's planning on doing something dangerous to get out of it.
-谢谢 是什么事...  -迈克尔他是个喜欢帮助别人的人
-Thanks.So what is it that you..  -Michael has a deep need to help people.
这我知道
So I've come to understand.
其实我们就是这么认识的
That's actually how we met.
那些把我带到这里的家伙
There were these men that brought me here.
曾告诉我我会有份好工作
Told me I'd have good job,
但那只是个谎言
but that was just a lie.
他们其实是要把我卖了
They were going to sell me.
他们那么做的时候 我...
And until they did,I...
是迈克尔花钱给我买了自由
Michael paid them off for my freedom.
但他不是要把我占为己有 像其他有些人那样
And not to keep me for himself,like I've heard from other girls,
而是给了我机会
but to give me an opportunity.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
是的 他是
Yes,he is.
尼卡 我会尽自己最大努力帮助迈克尔
Nika,I wanna do whatever I can to help Michael.
而在那么做之前 你得告诉我他卷进了什么事
To do that,I need you to tell me what it is you think he's mixed up in.
我想我不该来找你
I think this is a mistake.
-不 不 不是这样  -请照看一下他
-No,no,it's not at all.  -Please,just keep an eye on him.
不好意思
God,I'm sorry.
能留个电话给我吗 万一我...
Listen,could I just have a contact number for you in case...
我不觉得那是个好主意
I don't think that's a good idea.
请别告诉他我们见过
Please don't tell him that we met.
有件事我不明白
Something I don't get.
为什么杀了我就能阻止你
How could killing me stop you?
因为是我把伊科菲尔德公司的消息泄露出去的
'Cause I'm the one who leaked the information about Ecofield.
他们本有1000种方法掩盖这种事情
They could've covered up the scandal a thousand different ways,
可他们却偏偏选择伪装斯蒂德曼死亡
but they chose to fake Terrence Steadman's death.
并且选择了你
And they chose you
因为他们知道这会把我引出来
'cause they knew it would flush me out.
他们很清楚任何一个男人在知道自己无辜的儿子将被处死的时候
They knew that any man with a son on death row who was innocent
都会毫不犹豫的站出来
would have to come forward.
可是你没有
But you didn't.
我们有苦衷的 林肯
We had a cause,Linc.
我们有苦衷的
We have a cause.
那样就可以阻止他们的战争
Their wars can be averted
从而挽救成千上万的生命
and millions of lives can be saved.
所以你愿意牺牲一个作为代价
So you were willing to sacrifice one.
是的
Yeah.
至少我曾经这么想
At least I thought.
但我不能看着你死
But I couldn't watch you die.
你知道你做过什么吗
You know what you've done?
我孩子的母亲死了
The mother of my child is dead.
-我知道   -你知道?
-I know.  -Do you?
那你也一定知道迈克尔在狐狸河监狱
Then I'm guessing you know Michael's in Fox River
LJ在监狱等着受刑
and LJ's rotting in some jail.
-我都知道   -如果你能好好想想...
-I know all of it.  -If you think for a second...
你现在没得选了
You don't have a choice right now.
都是因为你 这所有的一切
This is all on you. All of it.
是的 我知道
Yeah,I know.
所以我才在这儿
That's why I'm here.
因为我还有机会弥补我的一些过错
'Cause there's still a chance we can make it right.
里面那家伙是我们的交通工具
That man in there is our transportation out of here,
也就是说 如果你现在去惹他麻烦
which means that,you go after him,
你也就搅乱了我和家人见面的机会
and that messes with my chances of me seeing my family.
所以我是不会允许发生这样的事的
So I ain't gonna let that happen.
你为什么不干脆把刀子给我呢
So why don't you just hand me that shank you're holding,huh?
很好
Good.
-嘿 莎拉   -嘿 瑞克
-Hey,Sara.  -Hey,Rick.
你没事吧
You all right?
我找不到钥匙了 能帮我开一下门吗
Yeah.I can't find my keys.Would you let me in?
当然可以
Oh,sure.
没想到会在这儿见到你
I'm surprised to see you here.
我也没想到
That makes both of us.
听着
Look.
你说得没错  我很抱歉
You were right and I'm sorry.
我不该把你卷进来的
I should never have gotten you involved in this.
没关系   -不 不是这样
-Oh,it's okay.  -No,it's not.
如果有谁知道我问你要...
If anyone knew what I asked...
我自己也不知道为什么这么做
I'm not even sure why I did it.
-谢谢  -现在我们扯平了
-Thank you.  -Now we're even.
你本来就没欠我什么
You didn't owe me anything.
不 我欠你很多 我欠你一切...
Yes,I did.I owed you everything,
但现在都结束了
but that's over now.
再会
Goodbye.
那女医生...
The lady doctor,
她在乎你
she cares for you.
贝利克
Bellick.
是警长 我想他有消息了
It's the sheriff.I think he's got something.
我是贝利克
Go,for Bellick.
我们刚接到一个废物回收站的电话
We just got a call from Steve Schimek up at the junkyard.
我们要找的野马车就在那儿
Our Mustang is on the premises.
他看见布伦斯了
He seen Burrows?
是的 我这有几个小组 估计最多10分钟后到达
Yes,I got a couple of units five,10 minutes away,tops.
好 我马上到
Good,I'm right behind you.
这个 你准备好了吗
Here.You ready to travel?
这周围全是警察 你知道的 不是吗
Place is gonna be crawling with cops.You know that,right?
沿河有条废弃的公路
There's an unimproved road down by the river.
那边可能没被封锁
There's a chance they haven't blocked it off yet.
我们有麻烦了
We got trouble.
快
Come on.
走这边
Through here.
快
Come on.
走吧
Get out of here.
走
Go.
转过身来
Turn around.
贝利克
Bellick!
贝利克 别开枪 别开枪
Bellick,don't shoot! Don't shoot!
原地跪下 跪下 跪下
All right on your knees!Right there! Right there!
想出来逛逛 是么
Thought you'd go for a little stroll,did you?
艾弗卡托的事听说了吗
Did you hear about Avocado?
他那玩意儿被切了
Got his salchicha sliced.
-怎么会   -特维那
-How?  -Tweener.
但艾弗卡托说是被铁丝扎下来的
But Avocado's saying it got caught on the frame
当他在床上乱蹦的时候
while he was hopping down off his bunk,yeah.
他为什么要说谎
Why did he lie?
不想特维那关禁闭
He doesn't want Tweener to go to the SHU
否则他就没法报复了
'cause he can't get him in there.
我想说的是 等艾弗卡托从医务室出来
All I have to say is,as soon as Avocado gets out of the infirmary,
特维那死定了
Tweener is a dead man.
钥匙的事进展怎么样了
How's that key coming?
-你车子上有吗 有时...   -我找过了
-What about your car? You know,sometimes...  -I just checked.
你家呢
Your apartment?
不在那里 因为今天早上我还用过
No,'cause I had them this morning.
那他们一定在这儿某个角落里了
Well,then,they gotta be here.
好好想想 你什么时候发现钥匙没的
Just retrace your steps.When did you first notice they were gone?
吃完午饭回来
When I came back from lunch...
我想看一下今天的探囚纪录
Hey,Kev,I need to take a look at that visitation log.
谢谢
Thanks.
迈克尔
Michael?
我需要知道他在哪儿
I need to know where he is.
-谁  -菲波纳奇
-Who?  -Fibonacci.
转变过程不仅需要我去寻求宽恕
You see,my conversion requires that I not only seek forgiveness,
也要求我宽恕别人 即使是我的最大的敌人
but provide forgiveness,even to my greatest transgressors.
别那样看着我
Don't look at me like that,
好像我还是以前那个老家伙似的 我不是了
like I'm the same old man I used to be.I'm not.
相信我 我需要找到菲波纳奇 这样我们才能重归于好
Trust me,I need to reach out to Fibonacci,so we can heal.
故事编得不错 但我不能告诉你
That's a good story,but the answer is no.
我明白
I understand.
我耐心等
I'll be patient.
你好
Hello.
从现在开始你正式靠边站
Hey,you're officially now on standby.
你要把她带到那边 明白吗
And you'll have her there.Do you understand?
我尽力
Yeah. I'll do my best.
我说了"你明白吗"
Hey,I said,do you understand?
是的 很响亮清楚
Yeah.Loud and clear.
很好 在歌斯公园的跑道上 你在地图上找找
Good.Goose Park airstrip.You can find it on a map.
我再打来的时候 你让那娘们在那边给我等着
As soon as I call,you have that bitch there ready and waiting.
还想让我偷那东西吗 你之前跟我讲的
You still want me to swipe the thing you were asking about?
我现在成了换季大甩卖了
'Cause I'm having a going-out-of-business sale.
你为什么不让自己被关禁闭
Why don't you get yourself to Ad Seg?
那样的话我就得承认 是我对艾弗卡托动的手
For that to happen,I'd have to admit what I did to Avocado.
那会再给我加个20年
That'd get me what,20 years?
不管怎么样我死定了
I'm dead no matter what.
也许还有一条出去的路
1There may be another way out of here.
是啊 装在尸体袋里
Yeah,in a body bag.
我需要知道我能否相信你
I need to know if I can trust you.
我像他们一样正直
I'm as straight up as they come,you know?
不 我是说完全信赖你
No,I mean really trust you.
-你好吗   -我很好 你呢
-How are you?  -I'm fine. You?
不错
Fine.
请把手伸出来
Can I have your hand,please?
-在这儿   -什么在这儿
-Here they are.  -Here what are?
你的钥匙就在你的收件箱里
Your keys,they were right over there by your inbox.
有个维修工等在外面
Well,you got a maintenance guy waiting outside here,
说你要他来换门锁
says you wanted him to change the locks.
要不要叫他回去
Want me to call him off?
不 叫他进来
No,send him in.
会不会打扰你们...
Is it okay if I...
没事 我快好了
Yeah.We're about done here.
有什么问题吗
Is there something wrong?
没有
No.
除非你想谈谈今早发生的事儿
Unless you want to talk about what happened this morning.
我想我有个更好的主意
I think I have a pretty good idea.
我们完了
We're done here.
我要他处于24小时监控下
I want him under 24-hour surveillance.
没我的允许连喷嚏都不能打一个
He doesn't sneeze without my knowing it.
这是干什么 我做错了什么
What the hell for? What did I do?
有人要杀我
Someone tried to kill me.
在距离这8英里的废物厂找到你 我可不敢苟同
Finding you in a junkyard eight miles from here makes me think different.
你的同谋呢
Who was your accomplice?
什么同谋
What accomplice?
24小时监控
24-hour surveillance.
头儿
Boss.
听说艾弗卡托那玩意儿在床上被切掉了
I heard Avocado cut his hose on your bunk.
一定是有什么剧烈的体育运动
Must have been some serious gymnastics going on.
我这次有事情要告诉你 头儿
I got something for you this time,Boss,
但我要求不能让艾弗卡托伤害到我
but I want guaranteed protection from Avocado,
减少我的户外运动时间
and I want time cut off my bid.
还有吗
Anything else?
要不要找个波霸全天伺候啊
Couple of big-canned whores available to you 24
相信我 我的消息绝对值这个价
Believe me,what I got is worth it.
你到底想不想听
So,are you gonna step up or what?
这是你最后一次机会 特维那
This is your last chance,Tweener.
你再乱弹琴 他们一定不会放过你
You blow smoke again,they'll be scraping you off the heel of my boot.
斯科菲尔德那帮干活的家伙
Scofield and his whole PI crew,
他们想越狱
they're escaping.